procoretech.com 2017-10-05

# Privacy Policy | Procore

**Effective Date: May 17, 2017**  
Welcome to the website of Procore Technologies, Inc. ("Company", "we", "us" and/or "our"). We have prepared this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain how we collect, use, protect and disclose information, It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information and data when you use the Company website ("Site") and Company services, including any software, mobile applications, products, devices or other services offered by Company from time to time and other services offered through third parties integrating Company functionality (collectively, "Services"). "You" refers to you as a user of the Site or Services.

**BY USING THE SITE OR SERVICES YOU CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged Procore Technologies.

#### PRIVACY SHIELD

Procore participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Procore is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework's applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce](http://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

Procore is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Procore complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Procore is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Procore may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party [dispute resolution provider](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request) (free of charge).

Under certain conditions, more fully described on [privacyshield.gov/welcome](http://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

#### PRIVACY FOR PROCORE PLATFORM USERS

Procore collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

Procore has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes on behalf of its Clients. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Procore's Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. Procore will retain this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### YOUR INFORMATION PREFERENCES

Upon request Procore will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. You can always review, correct, delete or update your Personal Information (defined below) by changing the relevant settings in your Company account or by [emailing us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

You can opt out of receiving certain emails by changing notification settings on the Site or in our applications, clicking the unsubscribe link provided in an email, or by [emailing us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com). If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please [email us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com).

####  INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Personal Information**  
We collect information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, username and password, phone number, company you work for and other personally identifiable information about you or users whose information you provide to us when you sign up for or use the Site or Services ("Personal Information"). For example, when you register for an account to use any of the Services, we collect your username, password, and email. When you create your account profile to use any of the Services ("Profile") we collect the Profile information you provide us to help you and others be located through the Services. When you add users through the use of our Services, we may collect information about the individual and the capacity in which they may use data within our application. The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not to provide the requested information, you may not be able to use some or all of the features of the Site or Services. Except in connection with your order to purchase Services, we do not collect any credit card or other financial account information. We also collect Personal Information from you when you access the Services and/or other parts of the Site and elect to provide Personal Information. For example, when you use the Services, we will collect data that you upload to the Site and/or information that you input into your account.

Our mobile application may collect certain additional information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device's unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, available storage space, connection type (e.g. WiFi vs. cellular) and information about the way you use the application. We may also use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location. If you do not want us to have your location information, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application.

**Usage Data and Site Activity**  
We automatically collect information regarding the actions you take on the Site and Services ("Usage Data"). Usage Data is information or content we collect about the use of our Site or Services in a way that does not identify an individual user. Usage Data helps us understand trends in our users' needs so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor our Services. This Privacy Policy in no way restricts or limits our collection and use of Usage Data, and we may share Usage Data about our users with third parties for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers' needs and improve our Services. When you use the Site or Services, some examples of the Usage Data we may collect could include: the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your web request, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, referring/exit pages and URLs, the pages you view and how you interact with links on the Services, comments and other content you post via the Services, the fact that you have posted comments, the time and duration of your visits to the Site or use of the Services and other such information. We may store such Usage Data itself and/or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Company affiliates, agents or service providers. We may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site or users of our Services, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, etc. We use this information to help us understand how people use the Site and Services, and to enhance the Site and Services.

#### TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and browser). We may also use Web beacons (a file placed on a website that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the experience of the Site and Services, such as pre-populating your username for easier login, to allow user-specific messaging or to permit user-specific advertising. We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. At this time, Company does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking, including "do-not-track" signals. You can remove persistent cookies and change your privacy preferences by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" directory. However, certain features of the Site or Services may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers may use their own cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, as further explained below.

We Procore and our partners use similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. To manage Flash cookies, please [click here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data and where the application was downloaded. We link certain information we store within the analytics software to authorized users for customer usage and metrics and to aid in customer success.

#### HOW WE USE INFORMATION AND WHEN WE MAY SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION GENERALLY

We may use and share your Personal Information for the purpose for which it was provided, including without limitation for the purposes described further below:

  * Provision and Monitoring of the Services: We will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to and to support your use of the Services and to monitor your use of the Services. We will also give you the opportunity to store, review and edit Personal Information and other information on the Site.
  * Surveys, Contests and Other Special Offers: From time to time, we may offer our users the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests and other special offers. If you elect to participate in these services, you will need to provide certain Personal Information.
  * Questions and Requests: If you contact us by e-mail or otherwise, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem.
  * Contacting You About Other Products, Services and Events: Company and, if you opt-in, third parties may use your Personal Information to contact you in the future to tell you about products, services and events that may be of interest to you.
  * Research and Data Analysis: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Site and the Services, Company may conduct research on its customers' and users' demographics, interests and behavior based on Usage Data and other information provided to us. This data may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Company may share this data with advertisers, researchers, business partners, publications, and other third parties. This information will not identify you or users personally.
  * Service Improvement: We may use your Personal Information, aggregated Personal Information and other non-personally-identifiable information collected through the Site and Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve the Services.
  * Order Fulfillment: We may use your Personal Information that you provide to fulfill any orders you may place for Services offered by Company.

If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, you may [contact us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com).

#### INFORMATION YOU MAKE AVAILABLE TO OTHERS

By using the Site or Services, including creation of a profile on Company or submission of public queries, you may make certain of your Personal Information available to others, such as your name or username. This information may be accessed by users who use the Site or Services and may be accessed by commercial search engines such as Google, Yahoo, and Bing to the extent that such engines are permitted to access the Site or Services.

#### SERVICE PROVIDERS

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses that we believe to be trustworthy and have privacy practices consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services, such as hosting and maintenance, accounting, data analytics and data storage and management, and marketing and promotions. We only provide our Service Providers with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by Company.

#### ADVERTISING

We also may share non-personally identifiable information with third party ad servers, ad networks, and data exchanges ("Advertisers") so that they can tailor their advertisements to your apparent interests and deliver those advertisements to you while you are either on our Sites or use our Services. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons to conclude that you have an interest in and to display a relative advertisement instead of a random advertisement. In addition, Advertisers use technologies (such as cookies, pixels, and Web beacons) to collect information about your browsing behavior on our Sites and via our Services which they may match with information they have previously collected (including personally identifiable information you have provided to them). Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that Advertisers may collect from you or that you choose to provide to them. For information about how to opt out of receiving certain behavioral advertisements, please [visit this website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) (or if located in the [European Union](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

#### OTHER TRANSFERS

We may share Personal Information and Usage Data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Company. If Company is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets or equity, we may disclose or transfer Personal Information and Usage Data in connection with such transaction.

#### COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS AND LAW ENFORCEMENT

In certain situations, Procore may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. Company will cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose Personal Information and any other content and information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion, we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to or comply with legal requests (including court orders and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of Company or of any third party, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

#### BE CAREFUL WHEN YOU SHARE INFORMATION WITH OTHERS

Please be aware that whenever you share information on a publicly available page or any other public forum on the Site or Services, others may access that information. In addition, please remember that when you share information in any other communications with third parties, that information may be passed along or made public by others. This means that anyone with access to such information can potentially use it for any purpose, including sending unsolicited communications.

#### EXCLUSIONS

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Company through the Site or Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Company shall be free, and you hereby grant Company the right, to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

#### SECURITY

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information and other information transmitted to us. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Site or Services, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Site or Services, and you do so at your own risk. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can [contact us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com).

#### SINGLE SIGN-ON

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address), with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to pose information about your activities on this website to your profile page to share with others within your network.

#### TESTIMONIALS

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. By posting a testimonial, you give your consent for Procore to use your testimonial in all media along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can [contact us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com).

#### BLOG

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, [contact us](mailto:privacy1@procore.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information.

#### SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our website. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.

#### THIRD PARTIES/LINKS

Our Site and Services may contain links or integrate with other websites and online services, or allow others to send you such links. Company is not responsible or liable for any damage or loss related to your use of any third party website or online service. You should always read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of a third party website or online service before using it, whether directly or in connection with your use of the Site or Services. Third parties may collect, but we do not authorize them to collect, personally identifiable information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use the Sites or Services.

#### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

#### NOTE TO INTERNATIONAL USERS

The Sites and Services are hosted in the United States and are primarily intended for and directed to users in the U.S. If you are accessing the Sites or Services from the European Union, Switzerland, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from U.S. laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Sites or Services, which are governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your Personal Information to the U.S., and you consent to that transfer. The laws in the U.S. may not be as protective of your privacy as those in your location. By using our Sites or Services, you agree that the applicable laws in the U.S. will govern the collection, use, transfer, and disclosure of your information.

#### PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will give you or our Client notice by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site prior to the change becoming effective. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. By continuing to use the Site or Services, you consent to the revised Privacy Policy.

**PLEASE PRINT A COPY OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY FOR YOU RECORDS AND PLEASE CHECK THE SITE FREQUENTLY FOR ANY CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

Procore Technologies, Inc.  
6309 Carpinteria Avenue  
Carpinteria, CA 93013
